General Reference; Collection ua950.002
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
General Reference Collection
1828-2015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua950.002
33 cubic ft.
A reference collection created by archivists that includes clippings, copies of official records, publications that document the University, students, alumni, and members of the faculty.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
All items in this collection were transferred, created or discovered by the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives. Generally these items were not part of organic collections or file series, but were deemed useful for researchers.
Administrative History
The M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives originates in the early 1971 with the establishment of the University Archives. The department was needed to manage the growing volume of public records created by the university after it had evolved into a major research university the previous decade.
In 1976 the department's first major outside collecting area was established with the tranfer of the German and Jewish Intellectual Émigré Collections from the New School with the help of Professor John M. Spalek. In 1982 the department started collecting materials on New York State politics and public policy, which became its largest area of focus. In 1996 the department was dedicated to former Profesor of English, M.E. Grenander. In 1999 the department moved to the specially-designed 3rd floor of the Science Library, and also began a joint effort with the Department of Criminal Justice to estblish the National Death Penalty Archive.
The principal purpose of the department is to collect, preserve, provide access to, exhibit, and encourage research use of the University Libraries' unique manuscript and archival materials, the official records of the University, rare books, and printed materials.
Scope and Contents
Contains class schedules, press releases on employee publications, fact sheets, promotional brochures, fliers, public notices, class schedules, departmental reports, club reports and a variety of other items that have not been included into more specific collections.
Arrangement
Collection was ordered alphabetically, and additions were interfiled periodically. The collection is also divided alphabetically by letter for easier viewing and navigation.
UAlbany Reference Collections; Clippings (Books, newspapers, etc.)
- A, 1828-2015; 1
  Scope and Contents
  This is an alphabetical letter series of the General Reference collection. The General Reference Collection was created by archivists to hold information on campus history that is not part of any organic record group. The collection contains material from a variety of outside sources, excepts from newspapers and other publications, press releases and promotional materials, and loose university records.
  - 4+2 Program, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abilities Awareness Month, 1993 April-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Affairs, Vive Presidents for, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Academic Activities Committee, 1974 February-1974 May (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Academic Calendar, 1949 November-1994 Spring (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Academic Honesty + Dishonesty Policy, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic Planning and Development Office, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Academic Program Abroad, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Academic Programs Abroad, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Academic Support Services, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Academic Support Services, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Academic Support Services, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Accounting Club, 1986 April (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Accounting Forum, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Accounting Society, 1976 March-1976 April (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Activities Day, 1967 September-1973 September (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for a Citizens' Lobby, 1964 July-1964 December; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Adirondack Life 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Admissions - University at Albany "Stepping Stones", Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Adopt a Needy Family Project, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Advanced Placement Teacher Workshops, Office of Summer Sessions, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Advisement Services Calendar, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Affirmative Action Grants, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Affirmative Action Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Affirmative Action Office - Affirmative Action Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Affirmative Action Office, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - African American Students, 1828-2018 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - African American Students + Graduates, ca. 2014 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - African and Afro - American Studies, Department of, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - African Students Association, 1978 May 6-1991 October 9 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Afro American Studies Graduate Regulations + Requirements, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - African National Congress, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Aging Research Coordination Project, 1975 June-1976 March; Undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - A Great Place to Be, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Albany Academic Programs Abroad, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Albany Architecture, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Albany Campus Events, 1975 February-1976 March (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Albany Collegiate Interfaith Center, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Albany Disabled Alert Program, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Albany Humor Society, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Albany In a Nutshell, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Albany Invitational, 4th Annual, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Albany Jewish Community Collection & Archives 1979 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Albany Review, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Albany Rural Cemetery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Albany Small Business Development Center, Undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Albany Small Business Development Center, 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Albany State Archers, 1976 January-1977 February (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Albany State Christian Fellowship, 1986 September (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Albany State Cinema, 1971 September-1976 September (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Albany Student Coalition Against Racism, 1975 February-1977 March (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Albany Student Press, ca. 1968 December-1979 December 7 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Albany Student Union, 1978 April-1978 September (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Albany State University Back Association, ca. 1986 February (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Albanysux.com Webpage, printed 4/12/00, 2000 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Albany Towers Investment Club, 1967 March-1969 November (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Alice Hastings Murphy Scholarship, ca. 1996 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Alcohol + Drug Use Policy in the Workplace, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - All African People's Revolutionary Party, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - "The James E. Allen Collegiate Center: An Experiment in Undergraduate Education", by Thomas E. Pullybank. Funds of the Libraries' Sesquicentennial Historical Essay Award Conference + Winner, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Allen Collegiate Center bulletin 1975 - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Alliance Francaise, 1973 December (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Alma Mater, 1969-1982 December; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Alpha Chi Rho Fraternity Interfraternity Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Alpha Epsilon Pi Fraternity Alpha Nu Chapter, recognized by National 1986 Interfraternity Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi (sorority), Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Alpha Epsilon Phi Sorority Eta Chapter, recognized by National, 1917 - 1955, inactive 1955 - 85, est. 1985 SUNYA Panhellenic Assoc. of Sororities, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Alpha Iota (sorority), ca. 1952 November-1953 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority Nu Psi Chapter, recognized by national 1981 Pan Hellenic Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Alpha Omicron Phi Sorority Delta Psi Chapter, recognized by National 1989 SUNYA Panhellenic Association of Sororities, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Alpha Phi Gamma National Honorary Journal in Fraternity, 1967 January-1968 September (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Alpha Phi Sorority Eta Nu Chapter, recognized by national, 1989 SUNYA Panhellenic Assoc. of Sororities, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Alpha Pi Alpha (fraternity), 1952-1978 February; Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Alpha Tau Omega Fraternity Interfraternity Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Alpha Xi Delta Sorority, SUNYA Panhellenic Association of Sororities, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Alumni Affairs Office, ca. 1967 August-1986 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Alumni Association, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Alumni Association - Class Councilors, 1920-1993 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Alumni Association - Constitution + Bylaws, 1947 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Alumni Association - Florida + West Central Florida Branch 1926 - 49, 1966 - 67, 1981(?) -, 1988 Spring-1998 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Alumni Association - Florida Branch, ca. 1998 July 15 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Alumni Association Governance Documents, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association History Time - Line, 1849 - 1999 be Geoff Williams, Katherine Chansky and Kevin Glick (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association History Time - Line, 1849 - 1999 be Geoff Williams, University Archivist (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Association Logos, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association Timeline for 150th Anniversary, 1999 June 04 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Councilor, Class of 1953, ca. 1955 June 3-1972 March (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Day, 1993 June 12 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Alumni House/Conference Center Center, 1976 Spring (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Alumni House - Grandfather Chime Clock, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Memorial Window, Willetts Street Building, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Alumni, Prominent, 1996 May 16 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Quad Productions, 1986 April (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1984-1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Amateur Radio Club, 1975 February-1984 Spring (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - American Cancer Society - Jail - N - Bail, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, 1974 October-1875 February (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1968 September (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - American Institute for Economic Research - Empiricism in Clinical Practice, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - American Society for Aesthetics - Experiencing Space: Architecture, Dance and the Designed Environment, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - American Society for Public Administration Empire State Capital Area Chapter Rockefeller College, SUNYA, 1991 April 25 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Studies Program, 1974-1977 May (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act Taskforce, Final Report, ca. 1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Amnesty International, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - An Act For the establishment of a Normal School, Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Anniversaries, Centennial Celebration, 1943 March-July 1944; Undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Anniversaries, Semi - Centennial Jubilee, 1894 June (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Anniversaries, Seventy - fifth, 1920 June (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Anniversary, SUNY Board of Trustees Resolution Celebrating 150th, 1993 December 14 (Oversized 1)
  - Anniversary Club, 1973-1983 October (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Anniversary Exercises, 1903 June-1912 May (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Annual Fund, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Annual Fund, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Annual Reports of the New York State Normal School at Albany, 1870-1872 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Anthropology Club, 1972 January-1977 May (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Anthropology, Department of, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Anti - Apartheid Committee, SUNY Albany, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Anti - Imperialist Student Movement, 1973 April (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Anti - Sexist Men's Discussion Group, 1978 September (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - "Anti - War Activism...1970"Paper by Rob Irwin, 1991 Fall (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Appointment Bureau, 1927 November-1934 June (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Apollo Agonists: The Humanities in a Computerized World April 19 - 21, 1979 (Institute for Humanistic Studies Sponsored Conference (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Archaeological Institute of America, 1977 October (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Art Coordination Committee, 1965 September-1971 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Art Coordination Committee, 1972 September-1974 June (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Art Council, 1964 May-1973 January (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Art Exhibits, Faculty, 1949 February-1955 September (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Art Museum, University at Albany, 2015 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Asclepius at Syracuse: Thomas Szaz, Libertarian Humanist Conference, April 17 - 19, 1980 (Institute for Humanistic Studies Sponsored Conference) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Asian Studies: Nanyang University in Singapore, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - ASRC Report, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - ASP Articles, 1968-1985 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - ASP Articles Index, 1968-1985 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - ASRC Report, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Assistantships and Fellowships, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Assistantships and Fellowships, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Associate of Council Members and College Trustees of State University of New York, 1971 November-1972 October (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Association for Women in Science (AWIS), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York, 1951-1973 September (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Association of Men's Intramural Athletics, 1970 September-1978 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Association of New York State Teachers College Faculties, 1936-1962 April; Undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Association of Teachers College and Normal School Faculties of New York State, 1934 October (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Astronomical Society, 1977 February (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Athena, Published by Women's Liberation Group of SUNYA, 1974 - 75, Feminist Alliance, 1975 -, 1974-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Athletics and Recreation, 1962-1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Athletics and Recreation, 1972-1985 October (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Athletics, Baseball, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Athletics, Basketball, 1972-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Athletics, Basketball, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Athletics: Basketball, Mens, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Athletics: Basketball, Womens, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Athletics: Division II, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Athletics: Field Hockey, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Athletics, Football, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Athletics, Football, 1989-1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Athletics, Gymnastics, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Athletics, Hockey, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Athletics, Judo, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Athletics: Karate, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Athletics, Lacrosse, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Athletics + Recreation, Dept. of, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Athletics, Rowing, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Athletics, Rugby, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Athletics, Sailing, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Athletics, Scuba Diving, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Athletics, Soccer, 1955-1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Athletics, Swimming, 1969-1984 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Athletics, Table Tennis, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Athletics, Tennis and Golf, 1968-1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Athletics, Track and Field and Cross - Country M+W, 1968-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Athletics, Volleyball, 1976 October 7 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Athletics - Women's Rules for Varsity Basketball, Regional in Alumni Memorabilia Collection, 1926-1929 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Department, ca. 1963-1987 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Atmospheric Sciences Research Center: Science Lectures, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Authors + Editors Program, 1990-1994 October 12 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Awards and Honors, 1965-1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Awards for Excellence, 1978 September-1986 October 03 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Awareness Day, 1979 April (Box 3, Folder 38)
- B, 1844-2002; 2
  - Baccalaureate Services, 1912 June-1965 June (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bahai Faith, 1974 March (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Barnes & Noble, 1998 October 28-1999 September 1 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Barron's, 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bayens, Margaret Hoefner Class of 1949, Undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Benevolent Association, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Beta Beta Beta, Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Beta Phi Sigma, 1971 October - 1980 April (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Beta Zeta, 1932 November-1973 February; Undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Beta Zeta, Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Biochemistry Program, Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Biological Research in Aquatic Sciences Conference, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Biological Science Dept., 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Biological Science Dept. of Telephone Directory, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Biological Science, Graduate Program, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Biology 411, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Biology Club, 1972 February - March 1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Biology Bio 410 Lab Manual, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Biomedical Sciences, Dept. of, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Black Action Coalition, 1974 November - March 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Black History, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Black Student Union (Umoja), 1972 January-1972 March; Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Black Students Alliance, 1968 November - 1969 January; Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Black Week Experience, 1971 April (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Black Weekend, 1970 April - 1973 April (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - The Blackfriars, 1932 October (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Blood Drive, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bloodmobile, 1968 December (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees Naming of Buildings and Grounds Policy, 1980 September 22 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Boor Sculpture Studies, 2002 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Boor Sculpture Studies, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Borinquen Enlightenment, 1974 October (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Boulevard Cafeteria Ticket for Alumni Association, 1940's (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bread & Roses Award, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bread and Roses Award for Excellence in Service, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Bridge Builders, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Bridge Club, 1975 July (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Briere, Eloise, Professor of French Studies, 1982 - 2012 December (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Briere, Jean - Francois Professor of French Studies Languages, Literature, and Culture 1979, 1979 - 2012 December (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn (poet, received honorary degree), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Brown, Francis J., Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Senator Joseph L. Bruno Biotechnology Development Center, 2000 September 22 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Budget Allocation Procons, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Budget Committee, 1979 February-1979 March (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - "The Budget and The Academic Library"Conference (School of Information Science and Policy), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Budget Office, 1969 March - 1974 March (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Budget Office, 1974 April - 1981 January (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Buildings, Alumni House Conference Center, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Building Architects, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Buildings Biology Building, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Buildings, Center for Environmental Sciences & Technology Management, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Buildings, Downtown Campus, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Buildings, Downtown Campus, 1908 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Buildings, East Campus (East Greenbush), Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Buildings - East Campus, 1996 November 1 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Hawley Building Floor Plans, 1909 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Buildings - Gideon Hawley Building (Downtown Campus), Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Buildings - Main Campus, 1963 July (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Buildings - Lodge + Howard St., 1849-1885 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Buildings, Page Hall see also residence Halls: Page Hall, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Buildings - Presidents' Mansion 5 Englewood Place Robert Williams Gibson architect, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Buildings - Science Library, Electronic Library, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Buildings - State Street (115 - 121), 1844-1849 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Buildings - Willet Street 2nd Permanent Building, 1885-1906 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Buildings & Grounds - Naming, 1935 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bursar, 1970 March (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - John E. Burton Lecture & Awards Ceremony Nelson A. Rockefeller College J. Public Affairs & Policy, 1994 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Business Administration Department, 1971 September (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Business Forum, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Business, School of, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Business, School of, 1988-1990 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Business, School of, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Business, School of First Year Progress Report 5 Year Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - School of Business Ph.D. in Organizational Studies, Undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - The School of Business, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Buyer's Day for Minority and Women Owned Businesses, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Bus Service, 1964 November (Box 4, Folder 65)
- C, 1845-2015; 3
  - Calendar Committee, 1964 September - 1965 January (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Calendar of Events, 1962-1970 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Calendar of Events, 1972-1976; Undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Camera Club, 1974 January - 1978 February (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Campaign for Albany, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Campus Academic Plan, 1964-1967 August (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Campus Academic Plan, 1968; Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Campus Action, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Campus Bible Fellowship, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Campus Center, 1967 January-1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Campus Center, 1973 January (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Campus Chest, 1958-1972 November (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Campus Children's Center (See also Dutch Quad Child Care Center), 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Campus Christian Council, 1963 January-1972 May; Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Campus Coalition, 1973 March (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Campus Communication Group, 1973 April (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Campus Conference, 1994 September 22-1994 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Campus Crusade for Christ, 1972 March (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Campus Forum, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Campus Guide and Directory, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Campus in Print, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Campus Life Office, 1984 July (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Campus Map, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Campus Ministry, 1964 January-1977 October; Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Campus Pond, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - "Campus Priorities and Resources", 1977 September (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Campus Profiles offices of Industrial Research, 1992 February (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Campus Safety and Security, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - "Campus Security Services in State University of New York: A Report of the Task Force on Campus Security, SUNY, 1975 October 15 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Campus Together Day, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Campus Unrest "The Academy in Turmoil"First Report of the Temporary Commission to Study the causes Unrest, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Capital Campaign, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - NY - Albany - State Capital 100th Anniversary "The Capital Centenary: Report of the Celebration of the 100th Anniversary of the State Capital In Albany", 1897 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Capital District Adult Educational Professional Development Consortium, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 29)